TAYLOR EISELE

SERVANT LEADER ♥ ST. LOUIS, MISSOURI, UNITED STATES 636-345-0894

• DETAILS •

St. Louis, Missouri United States 636-345-0894 taylorreisele@gmail.com

° LINKS °

LinkedIn

Personal Website

SKILLS

Adaptability

Fast Learner

Effective Time Management

Detail Oriented

Complex Problem Solving

Excellent Communicator

Inventory Management

Dedicated team player

Ability to Accept and Learn From Criticism

HTML/CSS/JavaScript

Zoom

Microsoft Excel

Microsoft Outlook

HOBBIES

Completing web development projects, attending St. Louis sporting events, fishing, traveling, reading, learning new things, volunteering.

PROFILE

Dedicated business leader with 8 years of experience in people leadership, learning & development, and eCommerce spaces. Highly driven to consistently exceed personal, team, and organizational goals. Regional Diversity & Inclusion champion committed to creating an environment where all are comfortable to be themselves.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Service & Engagement Manager at Target, St. Peters, MO

October 2021 — Present

- Consistently exceeding company goals for guest experience, improving year over year by 8+ points.
- Fosters team development through mentoring, coaching, and training towards personal career goals and business success.
- Partner with guests on feedback about experience to improve the business.
- Facilitates hiring, scheduling, coaching, and terminating of team members.
- Full ownership of guest experience in eCommerce business including operational metrics.

Facilitation Coach at Walmart, St. Charles, MO

October 2020 — October 2021

- Experienced in-person and virtual training facilitator.
- Demonstrated expertise and consistent support in delivering training to store-level hourly supervisors, assistant store managers, and store managers across 26 stores in 3 markets, ensuring continuous learning and development.
- Increased operational efficiencies by participating in content development for business-critical topics and changes.
- Improved productivity by collaborating with team members to effectively roll out company-wide change initiatives through hands-on learning and development while leveraging different technologies and resources.

Assistant Store Manager at Walmart, Chesterfield, MO

February 2018 — October 2020

- Assisted in the operation of a facility by leading and developing 300+ associates.
- Attained high customer satisfaction rating by delivering exceptional customer service standards and proactive engagement.
- Contributed to driving financial performance and goals by efficiently reviewing and evaluating Profit & Loss statements.
- Managed the hiring, developing, scheduling, promoting, and terminating of associates.
- Increased store eCommerce order capacity by 120%, resulting in 30% increase in eCommerce sales.

Customer Service Manager at Walmart, St. Peters, MO

August 2014 — February 2018

- Ensured efficient front-end operation and provided an excellent customer experience while leading 50+ associates.
- Motivated and developed associates to exceed customer expectations and prioritized work for the team to achieve business goals.
- Recognized professional resiliency while effectively resolving customer conflicts to retain business consistently.
- Oversaw all financial services transactions to ensure consumer and company safety from possible money laundering and scams.

EDUCATION

Diploma, St. Charles High School, St. Charles, MO